<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MoodBooster</string>
    <string name="title1">Exercise every day</string>
    <string name="title2">Be grateful</string>
    <string name="title3">Get enough sleep</string>
    <string name="title4">Keep your blood sugar steady</string>
    <string name="title5">Eat foods that nourish your brain</string>

    <string name="description1">Exercising for 30 minutes, three times a week has become outdated.
        While any exercise is good exercise, it’s more impactful to get moving, any way you can,
        every single day. Even just a brisk, short walk will energise you, help you sleep better
        and improve your mood.\n

        A University of Vermont study found that riding a stationary bicycle for just 20 minutes
        in the morning boosted mood and improved the ability to handle stress for a full 12 hours
        afterwards. The people who had exercised also reported less tension, anger, fatigue and
        symptoms of depression. For just twenty minutes of activity, that’s a major return
        on your investment!
    </string>

    <string name="description2">Numerous studies have shown an association between gratitude
        practices and well-being. Every night, right before I fall asleep, I do the ‘What Went
        Well’ exercise created by the father of positive psychology, Dr. Martin Seligman. I think
        of three things that ‘went well that day, reliving them in my mind and feeling the related
        good feelings. I also say a prayer of thanks for the things I’m grateful for. One of my
        coaching clients adds to this by writing in a journal one thing she is proud of having
        done that day, and one thing that she is looking forward to the next day. Create a
        gratitude ritual that works for you, as it will add richness and joy to your life.
    </string>
    <string name="description3">If you’re moody and irritable and routinely get less than seven
        hours sleep, there is a strong possibility that lack of sleep is the cause of your
        grumpiness. The less sleep you get, the more likely you are to feel stressed, sad, angry
        or exhausted. Make getting enough sleep a top priority, and you will be delighted by how
        much better you and your life feel.\n

        If you’re struggling to sleep well, here are some top tips on how you can get a better
        night’s sleep.
    </string>
    <string name="description4">To feel good throughout the day, make it a practice to never let
        yourself get too hungry, and avoid meals and snacks made from refined flours or sugary
        foods. Simple sugars and carbohydrates (like white flour and white sugar) cause your blood
        sugar to quickly spike and then crash, dragging your mood down in the process.\n

        Here are some tasty, healthy breakfasts to kickstart your day.
    </string>

    <string name="description5">Fatty fish like salmon, rich in omega-3 fatty acids, promote a
        healthy brain and better mood. I eat lots of fish and additionally take a wild salmon oil
        supplement. Eating a Mediterranean diet rich in fish, olive oil, legumes, vegetables and
        high-fibre grains is known to be wonderful for brain health and associated with reduced
        rates of low mood and depression.\n

        A final word: if you have been frequently experiencing a low mood, be sure to see your
        doctor. These tips are all useful for boosting mood but they are not designed to replace
        the care of a physician or psychologist.

    </string>


</resources>
